I was so preoccupied with my little buddy's brief recovery yesterday that I was hardly able to sleep.
Fitz was all I could think about.
And yet, not so much as a twitch from downstairs.
What a traitor.
At least I know all hope isn't lost, I guess.
Good morning, Master Luke.
How are you? A bit surprised to see you up so early.
Do we need to have a talk about Fitz?
I can't think of any reason we would.
Really? Not a single one?
Fair. I can see why you wouldn't trust me.
I may be repeating myself, Luke. I don't know.
But listen, I have no intention of opposing any of you.
I don't know anything about Master Fitz.
Or any secrets he might be hiding.
You're truly that willing to feign ignorance for us?
How come?
I've cut all ties with our family.
So I have no loyalty to them over you.
Moreover, I'm kind of afraid to get on the Princess's bad side.
And I would prefer to leave it at that.
The last thing I want is to make trouble for Fitz.
But this isn't going to be easy for me.
My body.
Your Highness, you asked for me to meet you, so…
I've been made aware that Rudeus approached us while we were out shopping the other day.
He was suspicious of your behavior.
And later, he threw you to the floor of the library,
and then you fled the scene shouting that you're a man,
or something like that according to the rumors.
It's concerning, because if he touched you,
I have no doubt he knows that's a lie.
This morning, Rudeus claimed that he was willing to keep your secret so as to not antagonize me.
However, I believe that he simply means to do right by a close friend.
I admire his devotion.
Now, what do you intend to do about this?
I completely understand you want to take your time.
No need to rush something so important.
However, after six months without any progress to speak of,
you have.
Even I've grown impatient.
I have to say something.
What?
And soon it will be your turn.
I've grown tired of watching you dither about something so obviously important to you.
So kindly work up the courage to reveal yourself to the boy.
And that's a direct order, Sylphie.
Princess, I…
What do you want most right now?
Really think about it.
To be frank, you've spent far too much time fretting over me.
Your debts have long been repaid.
It's time to think about yourself.
No, I can't.
I want to stay by your side because I care about you.
I know.
And holding back for my sake is your style.
But listen, you're not my servant anymore.
You're my friend.
So if you want something, I want you to put that first.
Stop prioritizing me.
I'll be just fine without you.
But that…
would be such a betrayal.
No, it most certainly would not, silly.
Now be brave.
Tell me what you want.
Then I guess…
I think…
What I want…
Is to be with Rudy.
Well done, Sylphie.
But…
If Rudy doesn't remember me, I don't think I'll ever recover.
So what am I supposed to say to him?
Don't worry.
We'll figure it out together.
Perhaps it would be best to keep things simple.
Why not just tell him you're the Sylphiette who grew up with him in Buena Village?
That may not work out.
If he truly doesn't remember her, the name may not ring any bells either.
Hmm…
Do any memories of your time together stand out?
Oh, let me think.
Well, um…
I believe I've told you about how I used to get bullied, haven't I?
Yes.
You mentioned that you were bullied for your gorgeous hair color.
I first met Rudy when he stepped in to save me from getting picked on.
I'd say that has to be my favorite memory of him.
Has anything else sprung to mind yet?
Not really. Sorry.
Wait, there is one thing.
When we met, Rudy actually thought I was a boy for a few weeks or a month at least.
But we got caught in a rainstorm while we were out practicing magic, and so we had to take a bath together back at his house.
He kinda… undressed me.
And then he pulled my panties down himself.
So, uh…
He saw my private parts.
And that's when he realized that I'm…
Um, actually… a girl.
I see. That's… quite the story.
Thank you for sharing.
I've finalized the details of our plan.
But before we start, do allow me to confirm one thing with you.
Oh, of course.
Sylphie, you said the other day that you want to be with Rudeus.
But I want to know what that means to you specifically.
What sort of relationship?
We would share a bed, and he can be crude sometimes, so he might say something like,
I want to put a baby in you.
Oh, but then I'll be crude too, so I could say something like,
Oh, Rudy, I'll take as many as you want to give me.
And then we'll go to our room.
Then he'll chuckle and he'll say,
I want to lie.
And we'll kiss and start undressing each other.
Then I'll laugh too and say something like,
Well, we better get started then.
You know, something like that.
Sylphie, your success here depends entirely on your efforts.
Oh, right.
Right.
Failures of nerve will not be tolerated.
If you come back and tell me that you once again couldn't find the courage to speak up when it counted.
By my authority as a princess of Asura,
I shall forbid you any further contact with Rudeus Greyrat for as long as you both live.
So give this your all.
Are we clear?
Yes, ma'am.
Wonderful.
Now then.
Let's discuss the plan.
Hm.
Rudeus?
Oh, Master Fitz.
What can I do for you?
Oh, well.
Can we talk somewhere else?
It's a bit sensitive.
Yeah, of course.
So, Zanoba, just go ahead with what we discussed.
Yes, sir. I have your notes and you can count on me to fill in the rest.
Okay.
So what's going on?
Uh, I actually have a pretty big favor to ask of you.
Well, rest assured. I'll be there with all the force of a red dragon.
Hold on a second. I haven't told you what it is yet.
Master Fitz, if it was for you, I would even shoot down a flying fortress.
Well, all right. So the thing is, Princess Ariel is frustrated because another noble keeps bragging about her bodyguard and at my expense.
Oh. Okay.
The noble tells her, and my Fitz has braved the forest of hail. He was only in a party of four. They brought back this flower that only grows there. Things of that nature.
A flower that only grows in the forest of hail. I guess that would be the freeze fringe. That blooms in winter.
Yes, well, after that, Princess Ariel had gone way too far to back down. And she might have said Silent Fitz could do that with an even smaller group, no problem.
Now I get it. Well, I'll tell you what. Let me ask around about the flower. I bet I could find you a deal on one.
What? Rudeus? No, no, no. That would just be cheating. I'm supposed to go out and show what I'm capable of.
Sure, but there's more than one kind of power. Having connections at your disposal is one of them.
Sorry, I can't do that. Princess Ariel would be humiliated if word were to get out.
I see. Okay. Oh, wait! Step leader is in town. I could get ahold of them.
No! Rudeus!
It's fine. Don't worry. We can set it up so they just coincidentally enter the forest at the same time we do.
But couldn't you and I pull this off? If you ask me, I think we'd be just fine without them.
I guess that's true. In which case, I would be more than happy to accept the job.
Thank you so much, Rudeus. I was so nervous about going into the forest by myself.
I'm sorry that I basically left all the prep work to you.
No, that's okay. And it's only natural if I'm the one playing bodyguard today.
Well, wait. Should I be paying you for your services then?
Of course not. I'm doing this because we're friends. I don't want anything from you. I'm just glad to help.
Right, but you don't have to be here at all, so the least I could do is pay you for your time, don't you think?
Well, I don't exactly come cheap.
I... I'm sure you don't, but still...
Buying Rudy with money?
Money?
Ah! Sorry! Uh, let's keep moving!
This flower blooms on a cliff.
I can melt us a path pretty much straight to it, but it's gonna take some paying attention.
Would you keep an eye out for threats while I do that?
I kept thinking about that staff after I fetched it for you the other day. It's really something.
I mean, all made to order with a colored magic crystal? I've never seen anything like it outside of the palace.
Yeah. A young noblewoman I tutored for a while gave it to me for my tenth birthday.
Do you think I could try holding it for a bit?
You've seen my beginner's wand, but that's all I have. I've always wanted to try out a staff.
Well, here. Go on, take it.
Got a good grip? Pretty hefty, right?
Yeah. It's so thick. Was this staff designed to be held with two hands?
I don't know. I thought it must have been sized for me to use when I grew up.
Huh.
Okay. All according to plan so far.
So, next.
Red Tower. I hope this works.
Perfect. Here we go.
A storm? Look at those clouds. We might be in for rain.
You're right. We should look for shelter.
It's fine. I'll have the sky clear in no time.
Oh no. Just like Rudy taught me, I'll gather moisture into the clouds, cool it, and let it fall.
Wow. I'm sorry, Master Fitz. I must be having an off day for some reason.
Oh, don't apologize. It's probably just because I'm still holding your staff, right?
I knew taking a staff away wouldn't stop him using magic. But I didn't expect I'd need to use it.
Well, not much we can do now that it's coming down. But look, there's a cave not too far up ahead. Might as well post up there for a while.
Uh, good idea.
This look okay to you?
Uh huh.
Hm.
There's been something fishy about this whole venture from the start.
Master Fitz has been acting weird ever since she hired me.
And now this sudden unseasonable downpour?
Someone may have created that storm with magic.
I wonder if Fitz has picked up on that.
She looks a little tense, which suggests to me that she has.
But she's still oddly calm.
Maybe she expected interference from that other noble's bodyguard.
Okay. That should do it for my clothes.
But what about my underwear?
I'm not really comfortable taking them off in front of Fitz.
I can dry...
Hm.
Hey, Master Fitz?
Y-yes?
What's the matter?
Um...
A girl I know told me that showing bare skin to members of a different race is taboo among elves.
So, to that point...
I'm going to turn around and keep my eyes closed.
You just change and get dried off, and let me know whenever you're done.
Mr. Fitz!
Please, at least take that coat off.
You're gonna make yourself sick, you know that, right?
Do you want me to make you a little stall or something?
Or maybe I could just leave the cave entirely, how about that?
That should work. I'll go right now.
Wait...
Come on. You'll get sick.
Yeah. You're right.
So let go. You can't stay in those clothes.
It could kill you. You're losing too much heat.
Yeah. I could die here. Unless you help me.
I can't seem to get my clothes off.
Undress me.
If you can't manage it yourself, then I suppose I'll have to.
You... you know...
I am already aware of the fact that you're actually a woman.
Yes.
But... I could still die here.
Unless you hurry and take my clothes off.
I could still take my clothes off.
But... I can't see it.
I can't see it.
Where have I seen those blushing ears before?
It's so familiar.
I can't see it.
But... that's why you're a little bit younger.
I heard it.
I didn't see it.
I'm sorry...
Where have I seen those blushing ears before?
It's so familiar.
Something like this happened to me a long time ago, didn't it?
When I was...
When I was five or six, maybe.
Moody, you're not quite done yet.
Master Fitz, I have a question.
What is it?
Ask away.
Is your name...
I mean, is your real name Sylphiette, by any chance?
Yes, it is.
That's right.
It's me.
It's Sylphiette.
From Buena Village.
I said it.
Finally.
Looks like she's still a crybaby.
More things change.
I waited.
I've waited so, so long.
And I worked really hard.
The whole time I was in Buena.
Yeah.
I know.
I love you, Rudy.
I've always loved you.
I loved you back then.
And now I love you even more.
Please never leave me again.
I want to stay with you forever.
I love you.
Bye.
I love you, Tommy.
I love you.
道 circle.
You are over.
Where is your fault?
Walking.
I love you.
I could be through life.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Aw, maybe.
I love you.
I want you to know you live in this special reality.
You, you, and you, and you, and your bishop make your entire house.
La-ya-la-ya-la